# Vladyslav Maidaniuk

(780)-271-2616 | Edmonton, AB, | vlad.maidanyuk95@gmail.com https://dear-ferdinand-page-aaf2rodhh-mydearferdinand.vercel.app https://www.linkedin.com/in/vladyslav-maidaniuk-32b6451a8 https://github.com/MyDearFerdinand

## **SUMMARY**

Responsible Front-End Developer with almost 3 years of experience in creating projects with perfect UI/UX solutions, solving and detecting bugs, and testing. Equally adept at developing software for PCs, online environments, and mobile devices.

Have strong skills of collecting, processing and mathematical analysis of data structures. I have excellent collaboration and communication skills as with teammates, as with other departments. Seeking full-time career as a Front-End developer and building roots in the community of Canada.

#### **Skills**

Languages: English - native, Ukrainian - native, Polish - native

Proficient with HTML5, CSS3 and Javascript | TypeScript, MySQL, ReactJS, React TS, Redux, RsJs, Node.Js, MongoDB, ExpressJS skills |

Mobile-responsive design | Associate experience with MERN stack | Some skills of APIs, Angular, Adobe, C#, C++ and Python

ASP.NET MVC, .NET Core | QA | Teamwork | Excellent written and verbal communication skills | Problem-solving | Fast learner

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Job Autopilot , Toronto ON, Canada

Jan 2023 - Mar 2023

Front-End Developer

- Work with the team of developers to improve software capabilities, optimisation and impact for corporate and non-corporate users.
- Performed style of application components with Scss features
- Developed from scratch fully responsive and adaptive kanban board-like tool with a lot of features, such as Drag-And-Drop dynamic cards with fetched from our back-end base data on them, using ReactTS and Redux technologies
- Collaborated with our UI/UX team to create an outstanding and minimalistic design
- Contributed my experience of web development to creative team in seeking engineer solutions and best practices for our website features

## Colombia moto tour, Gdansk, Poland

Mar 2022 - Nov 2022

Full-Stack Developer

- Improved an app performance
- Performed tasks related to the appearance of a web-page.
- Developed user interfaces and forms.
- Used WordPress REST API to improve website dynamic with adding adaptive sliders and increasing its responsivity
- Cooperated with UX/UI design team
- Improved mobile-responsivity of app UI.

## Contractor(Freelance), Gdansk, Remote, Poland

Jul 2020 - Mar 2022

Full-Stack/Front-End Developer

 Developed various app solutions using different coding languages, APIs and built frameworks, like HTML, SQL and JavaScript

- Worked independently on the development stage of many programs and services, where achieved strong problem-solving and troubleshooting skills.
- Developed applications from scratch, implementing new features for existing projects, and integrating with existing components with further maintenance and support.

# **EDUCATION**

College TEB, Gdansk, Poland	2021-2022
Associate Computer Science, Mobile web application developer  Udemy  Web Developing Maximilian Shwarzmuller's course  Coursera	2020-2022
C++ Basics	
Oles Honchar Dnipro National University, Dnipro, Ukraine B.S. at Sociology	2015-2019